Guide to the Yale University Building Project Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Central project records for Yale University building projects, circa 1976-2005; Accession 2007-A-090
  - Gustave Getter Consult. Engin. - Med School Chilled Water Study; 89000003, 1989 August (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Herbert Newman - Contract w/ Habitat for Humanity and Arch. School; 89000004, 1989 May (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Construction Consultants and Managers - WGS 4th floor Improvements, 1999 August (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Change Order - Leach Building Co. - Becton CCD 9, 2000 January (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Change Order - Leach Building Co. - Becton CCD"s 1-7, 2000 December (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Preconst. Requirements - Turner Const. - Chem Safety Building, 1992 February (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Change Order #9 - Tomlinson-H.-P. - Ingalls Rink, 1992 March (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Change Order 1 - McPhee Electric - Yale Mason and Helen Hadley -, 1999 March (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Agreement - Medical Repair Labs and Yale, 1995 July (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Agreement - Medical Repair Labs and Yale, 1992 July (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Yale - Hospital Cancer Center / Human Genetics Agreement, 1976 August (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Morse/Stiles Roof Perimeter Repairs; 4090901 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - ML Room 124 Renovation; 4051701 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - SSS, Woolsey, and UT Accessibility; 4050601 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Kline Geology Lab Room 218 Renovation; 4061801 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Osborne Memorial Laboratory - 1st Floor Renovations; 3052702 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - TEMP 432/434 Heat System Replacement; 4072601 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Sterling Law Building Rooms 122 and 124 AV Upgrade; 4081601 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - WALL53 Auditorium AC, 3rd Floor Renovation; 4062401 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Sloane Physics Lab Rooms 16 and 17 Renovations; 4061805 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Sterling Law Building; 4031801 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - 370 James Zone 3 and 4; 4051203 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - PARK 211 Interior Renovation - Phase 1; 3100110 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - WNSL Highbay Renovation; 3092501 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - PROS355 Site Improvements; 3072101 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - SSS 3rd Floor South Renovation; 3060301 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - HGS Bathroom Renovation; 3052203 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Lanman-Wright Hall Rehabilitation; 2111901 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Becton Engineering and Applied Science Center Lab 204; 2111401 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Becton Lab Rooms 212,212A,217 - Dunham Lab Rooms 103 C/D; 2080201 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - 55 Hillhouse Basement Renovation; 2041201 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - DL Undergraduate Space Renovation; 2032102 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - PWG Locker Room Renovation; 2021201 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - 52 Hillhouse Exterior Rehabilitation; 1122101 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Brandford and Saybrook Colleges Post Renovation Additions; 1121801 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Relocation of 285 Prospect Street; 1112902 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - UHSC Business Office; 1091901 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - SPL Passenger Elevator Renovations; 1060601 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - 55 Whitney - 5th Floor, Investments, Tenant Fit-out; 1111601 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Off-campus Shelving Facility - LSF Art Collections Fit-out; 1110102 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - PP Relocation, Tenant Improvements, Partial 1st and 2nd Fl 370 James St.; 1022202 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Yale University Art Gallery Library Shelving Facility - Phase 2; 1012501 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Davies Mansion; 1010401 (Box 2, Folder 65 - 66)
  - Vanderbilt Hall Renovation; 98022371 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Environmental Sciences Facility; 93111510 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - ML Elevator Modernization; 98022434 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - SBL York Street Offices; O4031801 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - James 370 Zone 3 and 4; O4051203 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - BR and SY PRV Replacement; O4061602 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - DL Undergraduate Space Renovation; O2032102 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - ML 214 Lab Renovation; O3012901 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Off-campus Shelving Facility, LSF Art Collection Fit-out; O1110102 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - 55 Hillhouse Basement Renovation; O2041201 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - 52 Hillhouse Exterior Renovation; O1122101 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Wall 53 AC - 3rd Floor Renovation; O4062401 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - PWG Locker Room Renovation; O2021201 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Congress Avenue Building; 98051801 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Congress Avenue Building; 98051802 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Congress Avenue Building - Core Facilities; O2092301 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - LEPH Architect Selection (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - 270 Congress Ave. YSM Instrument Shop; O2081201 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - LLCI B106-B110 Animal Facility; O2103101 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - LLCI Renovation; O2103001 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - LLCI B106-B110 Animal Facility; O2103101 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - LSOG Elevator Upgrade; O2061901 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - LSOG Elevator Upgrade; O2061901 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - LSOG/LCI Tunnel Asbestos Abatement; O3110701 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Magnetic Resonance Center; O3042501 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - MRC PET Center; O3042501 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - MRC PET Center Demolition; O3042501 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - KGL 218 Lab Renovation; O4061801 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - KGL 218 Lab Renovation; O4061801 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Morse/Stiles Roof Perimeter Restoration; O4090901 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - ML Room 124 Renovation; O4951701 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - OML Aquatic Modular Building; O4051702 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - OML 122, 126, 127 Lab Renovation; O3052702 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Peabody Museum, Master Plan Revision Feasibility Study; O4011401 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - 37 Hillhouse Ave Renovation and Addition; O2071901 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - 38 Hillhouse Ave Renovation and Addition; O2071901 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Survey and Mapping 405-437 Temple St., 2003 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Morse/Stiles roof perimeter reps; Hayden Building maintenance (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - ML Room 124 renovation, Fallon Company, LLC; 040517-01 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - OML Aquatic modular Building; 040517-02 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Peabody Museum, master plan revision feasability study; 040114-01 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Hillhouse, 37 Ave renovation; Paragon Construction Co.; 020719-01 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - 37 Hillhouse Ave, renovation and addition, Christopher Williams Architects; 020719-01 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - OML 122, 126, 127 lab renovation; P04150PCS; 030527-02 (Box 5, Folder 110)
- Building contract administration records, Accession 2008-A-029; 3.25; (4 boxes)
  Restricted until 1 Jan 2042.
  - Sprague Memorial Hall renovations, #980224-22, 2002-2004 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
  - 175/221 Whitney Avenue office renovation, #030114-02, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Central steam and chilled water distribution system, #303404-01, 2003-2006 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
  - OML 3rd and 4th floor renovation, #031113-01, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Environmental Science Center, # 031212-01, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 155 Whitney Ave., #041216-01, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ML 318 & 320 renovations, # 050513-03, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Woodbridge Hall accessibility, #980223-10, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - SSS fire protection improvement, #980223-41, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chemistry Research Building, #000121-02, 2000-2004 (Box 1, Folder 13-15)
  - KBT Infrastructure renovation, #010109-02, 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
  - KBT exterior renovation, construction phase#020501-03, 2003-2006 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - KBT exterior renovation, pre-construction phase services only, #020501-03, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Chemistry Research Building utility services, #021219-02, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 300 George Street Keck Foundation Mass Spectrometry Laboratory, #03025-01, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Edw309 miscellaneous renovation, #030729-03, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Beinecke/Hewitt Plaza rehabilitation, #031002-08, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - YUHS backfill office renovation, #031010-01, 2004-2005 (Box 1A, Folder 1-2)
  - Amistad Park remediation (parcel 3), #031105-10, 2004-2006 (Box 1A, Folder 3)
  - British Art Center inergen system, #040406-01, 2004 (Box 1A, Folder 4)
  - Sargent Drive 150 2nd IVF expansion, #041020-01, 2004-2006 (Box 1A, Folder 5)
  - SEAMCO, #05101201, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - George 300, #05101001, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - YPB, #00070601, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - NSB, #03081901, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - SHM, #03121601, 2004-2006 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Boardman, #04102201, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - YSM, #04061601, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Yale Standby, #04070801, 2004-2006 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - SHM, # 04090902, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - SHM Rotunda, # 04090903, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - YSM, #04091601, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - LMP, #04102801, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Yale Peptide, #04102901, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - YSM ESH, #03080402, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - TAC, #03092301, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Hope, #03100601, 2004-2006 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - YPB, #03100603, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - SHM, #0310604, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - YPB, #03101704, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - SHM Rotunda, #03100604, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - YSM, #03102301, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 21-22)
  - YSM, #03102702, 2004-2006 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Brady Memorial, #03110501, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - YSM, #03110511, 2004-2006 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - YSM, #04030501, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - LMP, #04030302, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - LMP, #04032901, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - FMP, #04042701, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - YSM, #04050401, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - BCCM, #04051202, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - LLCI, #04070201, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Hope, #04081901, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - George 300, #05100501, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - SHM, #05040705, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - SHM, #05012502, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - SHM, #05013101, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - HRT, #05091203, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - YPB, #01113002, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - YPB, #01111402, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - YPB, #01102901, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - SHM, #05012502, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - SHM, #02091802, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - SHM, #02032502, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - SHMI, #020724-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Beinecke, #202111-01, 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - SHMI, Chapel Construction, #020111-01, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Harkness Fire Protection, Chapel Construction, #020111-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - YPB change order, #011130-02, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - YPB contract, #011130-02, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - YPB change auth., #011130-02, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - BB3 North office renovation change order, #020326-01, 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - BB3 North change authorization, #020326-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - BB3 North contract, Turlington, #020326-01, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - BB3 North contract, Taulman, #020326-01, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Keck Clean Room, change order, #020705-01, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Keck Clean Room, contract, #020705-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Chemical Storage Room, change order, #020712-01, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - LSOG elevator, change order, #020619-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - LSOG elevator, contract, #020619-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - LSOG elevator, change authorization, #020619-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - SHB, change order, #020918-02, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - FMP-1, change authorization, #021211-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - FMP-1, contract, #020211-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - LLCI 2 Lab Restoration, change order, Taulman, #021213-01, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - LLCI 2 Lab Restoration, contract, Barkin, #021213-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - LLCI 2 Lab Restoration, change order, #021213-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - LLCI 2 Lab Restoration, contract, Taulman, #021213-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - IE 45 X-ray Crystallography, change order, #030128-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - YSM LH3, change order, #030205-01, 2003-2005 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - YSM LH3, contract, Babbidge, #030205-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - YSM LH3, early release, #030205-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - YSM LH3, contract, Tate & Burns, #030205-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - YSM LEPH 4, change order, #030227-01, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - YSM LEPH 4, contract, Whiting-Turner, #030227-01, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - YSM LEPH 4, contract, Svigals, #030227-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - YSM LEPH 4, change order, #030227-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - YSM LEPH 4, contract, Turner, #030227-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Harkness 2nd floor, change order, #000904-01, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Harkness 2nd floor, contract, #000904-01, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - YSM I2 L2 fire protection, change order, #001031-01, 2002-2005 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - YSM I2 L2 fire protection, contract, #001031-01, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - FMP, change authorization, Vander\weil, #040914-03, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - FMP, change, Taulman, #040914-03, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - FMP, contract, Taulman, #040914-03, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - FMP, change authorization, #040914-03, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - BCMM301-306, change, #041020-02, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - TAC S 652 B&C, change, #041103-02, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - LLCI 5, change, #050609-01, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - SHM I-wing, change, #050913-02, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - SHM I-wing, contract, #050913-02, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Sargent Drive 150, change, #020924-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Sargent Drive 150, contract, Svigals, #020924-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Sargent Drive 150, contract, Turner, #020924-1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Sargent Drive 150, contract, Taulman, #020924-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - LLCI-1, early release, #021030-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - LLCI-1, change, #021030-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - LLCI-1, contract, Tate, #021030-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - LLCI-1, change authorization, #021030-01, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - LLCI-1, contract, Tate, #021030-01, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - SHM I-wing elevator, change order, #021122-01, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - SHM I-wing elevator, contract, Babbidge, #021122-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - SHM I-wing elevator, change order, #021122-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - SHM I-wing elevator, contract, Chapel, #021122-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - SHM I-wing elevator, change order, #021122-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - FMP-1, contract, #021211-01, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - FMP-1, change, #021211-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - SHM I2/C2 fire protection, change, #001031-02, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - YPB, fire, change, Beckman, #010301-02, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - YPB, change, #010301-02, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - YSM L-wing emergency lighting, change, #010308-01, 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - YSM L-wing emergency lighting, contract, #010308-01, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Dermatology, #010726-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - SHM, #010726-04, 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Facilities project records, 1993-2007; Accession 2009-A-090
  Restricted until 1 Jan 2043.
  - Project Accounting
    - CHEFA DOCUMENTATION, 2007 April (Box 1)
    - CHEFA DOCUMENTATION, 2007 May (Box 1)
    - CHEFA DOCUMENTATION, 2007 June (Box 1)
    - CHEFA DOCUMENTATION, 2006 November - 2007 January (Box 2)
    - CHEFA DOCUMENTATION, 2007 January - March (Box 3)
    - CHEFA DOCUMENTATION, 2006 September - November (Box 4)
  - Project Management
    - Sterling Law Buildings - Phase 1 and 2 Audit File; 92101302 (Box 5)
    - Sterling Law Buildings - Settlement Agreement; 92101302 (Box 5)
    - Sterling Law Buildings - Renovation and Expansion Claims; 92101302 (Box 5)
    - Sterling Law Buildings - Phase 3 (Working File); 92101302 (Box 5)
    - Sterling Law Buildings - Phase 3 (Cost Estimates); 92101302 (Box 5)
    - SPP CH3 Replacement/Capacity Increase - Authorzation Number Change; 05050501 (Box 5)
    - SCL-KCL Renovatoin Study - Authorization Number Change; 03100206 (Box 5)
    - SHM I E Corridor Upgrade - Authorization Number Change; 03121601 (Box 5)
    - JE Renovation - Authorization Number Change; 04122101 (Box 5)
    - SML east side heating; 06071201 (Box 5)
    - MC/ES Renovation -original Contract; 06062801 (Box 5)
    - Amistad Street Building - Authorization Number Change; 02021301 (Box 5)
    - Brady/Lauder Addition and Alterations - Construction Audit (Box 5)
    - Lot 5 Parking Garage - Audit; 90050107 (Box 5)
    - Sprague Hall - Audit; 98022422 (Box 5)
    - Federal Audit (1993); N/A (Box 5)
    - Brady Addition and Alterations - Construction Audit (Box 5)
    - Chemistry Research Building; 00012102 (Box 5)
    - 1156 Chapel St. - Dimeo Audit; 97010903 (Box 5)
    - Chemistry Building - CM Selection (Box 5)
    - Congress Ave Building - Whiting Turner Audit; 98051801 (Box 5)
    - Congress Ave Building - Whiting Turner Interim Audit; 98051801 (Box 5)
    - Kline Biology Tower Priority 2 - Skanska Audit; 01010902 (Box 5)
    - SPP Capacity Increase 2002 -o and G Industries Audit; 99070902 (Box 5)
    - Becton Eng. and Applied Science Building; 96011901 (Box 5)
    - Berkeley College; 96071002 (Box 5)
    - Branford College; 98051503 (Box 5)
    - American Express Tax, Business Services Inc. and Belliveau Consulting LLC - Audits; N/A (Box 6)
    - E.S. Harkness Dormitory; 98051503 (Box 6)
    - ESF - Linbeck Audit; 93111501 (Box 6)
    - ESF - Phase 1 Insurance Claim; 98022443 (Box 6)
    - Fuel Cell Energy; N/A (Box 6)
    - Linsley-Chittenden Project; 92031705 (Box 6)
    - old Campus; 97090901 (Box 6)
    - osborne Memorial Lab; 97060301 (Box 6)
    - SDQ Adaptive Reuse; 96050901 (Box 6)
    - SHM b-Wing Extension; 00011301 (Box 6)
    - SHM I-Wing Child Study Center; 95051509 (Box 6)
    - Sterling Memorial Library Renovation; 93051704 (Box 6)
    - Saybrook College Renovation; 96071002 (Box 6)
    - Sterling Law Building; 97030701 (Box 6)
    - Vanderbilt Renovation; 98022371 (Box 6)
    - MBG Greenhouse 3; 05082603 (Box 6)
    - ML Elevator Modernization; 98022434 (Box 6)
    - ML 318 and 320 Renovations; 05051303 (Box 6)
    - ML HVAC Upgrade; 05062803 (Box 6)
    - Medical Area Electrical Upgrade; 03082101 (Box 6)
    - Metasys Controllers Upgrade; 06072101 (Box 6)
    - NRH Renovations; 06050801 (Box 6)
    - New Residence Hall (Box 6)
    - off Campus Shelving Facility; 97010902 (Box 6)
    - oML 3rd and 4th Floor Renovations; 03111301 (Box 6)
    - oML Utilities Tunnel Replacement; 05020303 (Box 6)
    - oML 226 and 220 LabRenovation; 06063001 (Box 6)
    - PSPS - Claim by Consolidated Contracting; 98022303 (Box 7)
    - PSPS Rehablitation; 98022303 (Box 7)
    - 205 Park Street Basement Safety Renovation; 06080402 (Box 7)
    - 211 Park Interior Renovation; 05070102 (Box 7)
    - Payne Whitney Gym Exterior Renovation; 05021501 (Box 7)
    - Phelps Elevator Upgrade; 05080402 (Box 7)
    - Pierson College Renovation; 98022375 (Box 7)
    - 100 Prospect Temporary LabRenovation; 05082601 (Box 7)
    - Prospect St. Planning Study (Box 7)
    - 77 Prospect St. and 87/89 Trumbull St. Renovations; 02052901 (Box 7)
    - 100 Prospect Temporary LabRenovation; 05082601 (Box 7)
    - 365 Prospect New Parking Lot; 05032301 (Box 7)
    - SDQ Marquand Chapelorgan; 04052102 (Box 7)
    - SDQ HVAC Upgrade; 04102101 (Box 7)
    - SDQ Solar Panels; 05062402 (Box 7)
    - SDQ East Exterior Renovation; 05111601 (Box 7)
    - SDQ YDS Exterior Renovation; 05111602 (Box 7)
    - SDQ; N/A (Box 7)
    - SDQ East Exterior Renovation; 05111601 (Box 7)
    - SDQ, Marquano Chapelorgan; 04052102 (Box 7)
    - SDQ YDS Exterior Renovation; 05111602 (Box 7)
    - SDQ Hot Water Line Replacement; 06060804 (Box 7)
    - Development Capacity Study; 06092801 (Box 7)
    - SPL Rooms 52 and 53 Renovation; 04070202 (Box 7)
    - SMH Renovation; 98022402 (Box 7)
    - Ingalls Rink Cooling Tower and Zamboni Facility; 04011603 (Box 7)
    - Ingalls Rink Evaporative Condenser Replacement; 04011603 (Box 7)
    - IR Study; 06102401 (Box 7)
    - 370 James St. Control Center Relocation; 05100703 (Box 7)
    - 370 James St. 1st Flooroffice and Shop; 05100702 (Box 7)
    - 370 James St. 2nd Floor Customer Service Fitout; 06031002 (Box 7)
    - 370 James St. 1st Floor Shopoffices CRAF07; 06121201 (Box 7)
    - Jensen Plaza Study; 06072701 (Box 7)
    - K, PM, 38HLH, WNSL Elevator Cylinder Replacement; 06031702 (Box 7)
    - Leigh Hall Renovation; 02022201 (Box 8)
    - Leitnerobservatory Renovation; 04122102 (Box 8)
    - Lewis Walpole Library Addition; 03050601 (Box 8)
    - Long Term Pakring Study; 06010404 (Box 8)
    - 63 Locke Acquisition; 98022331 (Box 8)
    - PC Renovation; 98022375 (Box 8)
    - Pierson Sage Parking Structure; 98022303 (Box 8)
    - 200 York and Rudolph Building; 98022312 (Box 8)
    - Rudolph Building Renovation; 00121501 (Box 8)
    - Rudolph and Art History Building; 00121501 (Box 9)
    - Pierson College Renovation; 98022375 (Box 9)
    - SLbAdditions and Renovation (Box 9)
    - Trip Report, Jamestown Chemical Company, Drew Water Systems and NALCO Chemical; N/A (Box 9)
    - GEoandM and Contractual Service agreements; N/A (Box 9)
    - Purchaseorder Approval Check List (PO# YKF1072851); N/A (Box 9)
    - Purchaseorder Approval Check List (PO# YKF1077086); N/A (Box 9)
    - Water Treatment Agreement; N/A (Box 9)
    - Purchaseorder Approval Check List (PO# YKF1080414); N/A (Box 9)
    - Amistad Parcel 3; 03110510 (Box 9)
    - SLbPhase 3 (Working File); 92101302 (Box 9)
    - Yale Law School - Completion of Phases 1 and 2 (Box 9)
    - 200 York; 98022312 (Box 9)
  - Project Accounting
    - CHEFA DOCUMENTATION, 2007 September (Box 9)
    - CHEFA DOCUMENTATION, 2007 July (Box 10)
    - CHEFA DOCUMENTATION, 2007 August (Box 10)
    - CHEFA DOCUMENTATION, 2007 October (Box 11)
    - CHEFA DOCUMENTATION, 2007 November (Box 11–12)
    - CHEFA DOCUMENTATION, 2007 December (Box 12)